Hello
and welcome to our course
on the input metrics.
I'm Bill Carr
and I spent 15 years at Amazon
as the Vice president of digital media.
I'm Colin Bryar.
I spent a little over 12 years at Amazon
as a technical vice
president, and two years as Jeff
Bezos's chief of staff.
This course will enable you to achieve,
first,
a deep understanding
of the concept of input metrics.
Second, to identify input metrics
for your business, product operation
or function.
Third, to measure and analyze your inputs.
Fourth, to be able to conduct
an effective weekly business review.
And finally, fifth, to implement
and use the Weekly Business
Review Reporting Tool
to visualize your metrics.
For each lesson, we'll share.
Real world examples to help
you understand the practical applications
of these principles and practices.
In addition, you'll have access
to our library of related
documents, templates,
and tools to download, read, and use.
Give a group of smart people
a big goal, such as an aggressive revenue
target, and trust
they'll figure out how to do it.
That's the way a lot of companies
try to optimize their business.
And that's what we did at Amazon
in the early days, too.
In 2000,
after roughly five years in business
at Amazon, we realized that this method
wasn't working for us.
The business was getting more complicated.
We weren't serving our customers
well enough, and we were not achieving
our desired outcomes
as consistent as we wanted.
We had a choice to make.
We could double down on our approach,
rely on good
intentions, and ask people
to try harder to hit their goals.
Or we could
plot a new course of action,
one of process control.
The required us to learn new skills,
apply them rigorously and consistently.
We chose this latter path
and it has paid dividends ever since.
Every business can be viewed as a process
and processes
have both inputs and outputs.
We were too focused on the outputs.
Moreover, a process like Amazon's
retail business
can be decomposed
into many smaller processes.
Rather than ask teams
to optimize their output metrics
and leave them up to their own devices.
We asked them to identify their outputs
and inputs.
Then we gave them tools to reduce
the variation, improve the weekly average
for their input metrics,
which in turn improves output metrics
like active customers,
sales, revenue, and profit.
So why should you care about input metrics
in this course?
Well, there's two big reasons.
First,
this course is going to give you knowledge
and tools to gain
a better operational grasp of what drives
your business
so you can achieve your desired outcomes.
Second, by consistently
studying your input and output data,
you can't help but feel the customer
pain points,
which forces you to develop ways
to fix them.
This continuous stream of that data
becomes the raw material
that will spur innovation.
But now let's
get started with session one.